I've had enough!
我受够啦
Stop!
停停停
Honey,
老婆
I'm coming.
快 快 快
Here they are.
锵 锵 锵
Honey, look
老婆看
at these big, red cherries.
又红又大的车厘子
They're super sweet,
特别甜
the highest grade,
五个级别的
as big as pigeon eggs,
跟鸽子蛋一样的
absolutely delicious.
好吃极了
Who told you to buy this?
谁让你买这个的
Are you trying to raise my blood sugar
嫌我血糖升得不够高
even higher?
是不是
Do you want me to die?
是不是想让我死
Honey.
老婆
Wait!
不对
Do you want me to die
是不是我死了
so you can find someone else?
就可以找别人了
Honey,
老婆
don't talk like that.
可不敢胡说
Sit down.
宝贝 来 坐
Don't be mad.
不生气啊
We're not eating it.
不吃了
It's too sweet and it'll make throat dry.
它太甜了 齁嗓子
We won't eat this.
真不能吃这个东西
Your favorite brand of shoes
你最喜欢那个牌子
has a new collection. It's beautiful.
鞋上新款了 特别漂亮
It's like crystal boats,
水晶船一样的
all sparkly.
上面唰唰唰
Jia Haowen,
贾浩文
are you trying to annoy me on purpose?
你是不是故意恶心人
My feet are already
我的脚现在肿得
swollen.
都大了两码了
Crystal boats?
谁穿水晶船
I want crystal shoes.
我要穿水晶鞋
Alright.
好的
Honey.
老婆
We won't wear them.
咱不穿
After we have the baby, swelling goes down,
等咱生完孩子
then we'll wear them.
咱脚消肿了咱再穿
Let's just buy them
买到这儿
and keep them at home to look at.
放在家里咱看
Let's go buy a bag.
买包去
A new collection.
最新款的包
It's beautiful.
很漂亮
A popular beach bag,
沙滩包特别流行
very roomy.
特别能装
Are you saying I'm good at acting?
你说谁能装
You are saying I'm good at acting.
你说我能装
Jia Haowen!
贾浩文
You've learned
你现在都学会
to insult people indirectly now.
指桑骂槐了
Honey,
媳妇
I wouldn't dare!
我哪敢指桑骂槐啊
You can scold me directly,
你要骂我都不用走程序
no need for indirect insults.
直接骂
You can even hit me
上手也可以啊
if you want!
老婆
Honey...
媳妇
Darling...
媳
Give me a knife.
给我拿把刀
I'll cut everything in the house in half.
家里东西都劈两半
Let's live separately.
各过各的
Honey.
老婆
Don't touch me.
别碰我
Live separately.
各过各的
Honey,
老婆 老婆
let's go buy a house.
买房去
The apartment you like the most.
你最喜欢的公寓
Live separately.
各过各的
Honey,
老婆
don't eat too much.
少吃点
It's too sweet.
太甜
It is the most
这一套可是
in-demand layout.
最抢手的户型
Three large rooms, with great lighting
大三居 南北通透
and ventilation, an open kitchen and bathroom.
采光特别好 明厨明卫
Perfect for both investment and living.
不管是投资还是自己住
But there aren't
特别合适
many left.
但是现在没几套了
Did you hear that?
听见没有
Not many left.
没几套了
Got it, honey.
媳妇 明白
I'll pay right away.
我这就刷卡
Yanzi,
燕子
take Mr. Jia to sign the contract.
带贾先生签合同去啊
Alright, where is it?
好好好 在哪儿
I use my strategy
这套房
to get this house.
是我跟他作过来的
What's this, a bitter scheme?
演的哪一出啊 苦肉计
Who cares?
管他什么计呢
He said he'd buy me an apartment.
他说要给我买套公寓
Let's finalize it quickly.
赶紧敲定
Mengxin,
梦心
I know you're thinking of me.
我知道你心里想着我呢
I just have performance pressure.
我这不业绩上有压力嘛
Please, don't think that way.
你可别这么想啊
I've always
一直以来啊
wanted to have a house
我就想要有一套
of my own,
属于自己的房子
a place I could decorate
可以按照自己的喜好呀
and design according
去布置它
to my tastes,
装修它
to turn it
把它打扮成
into the home of my dreams.
我理想中家的样子
You know,
你也知道
after having kids,
有了孩子之后呢
everything starts to revolve around them.
处处要为孩子考虑
I just wanted a space
我就想要有一个
where everything
很纯粹的空间
is what I like.
一切都是我喜欢的
Wouldn't that be wonderful?
这多好啊
Now your dream
那你现在梦想
has finally come true.
终于实现了
Thanks to you.
多亏有你啊
Mengxin,
梦心
this is the first house I've sold
这是我做销售以来
since I became a real estate agent,
第一套房子
and it's all thanks to you.
就是你帮我开张的
Once I get the commission,
我拿到佣金以后
I'll treat you to a big meal.
请你吃大餐
Yeah!
吃大餐
Actually, I should be thanking you.
其实我应该谢谢你
It was your idea
是你说的
to invest in real estate
让我投资房产的话
that inspired me.
启发了我
Did you know?
你知道吗
Haoze's mom
浩泽妈妈
got kicked out of the villa.
被赶出别墅了
And now, another woman
那个别墅又住进
has moved in.
别的女的
She even brought her child.
还带着孩子呢
I heard Haoze's mom
听说浩泽妈妈
is now staying
现在只能带着孩子
in a hotel with her child.
住在酒店里
I need to be prepared, too.
我也要防患于未然
I've been hearing too much gossip lately.
最近离婚八卦听太多了
The more I hear, the more uneasy I feel.
越听越不踏实
Mengxin, you're always
梦心 你这天天的
listening to this gossip every day.
听这些八卦 是非
Is this for prenatal education?
做胎教吗
No, I...
没有 我
I'm just killing time.
我这不闲着没事干吗
How's it going with the baby's dad?
你跟孩子她爸
How are the talks?
谈得怎么样
Still talking.
还在谈着呢
Let me tell you,
我跟你说啊
you must fight for the best
一定要为自己和孩子
interests for yourself and the child.
争取最大的利益
Don't ever suffer losses
千万不要为了什么
in the name of so-called dignity.
所谓的尊严吃了亏
If it doesn't work out,
不行啊
get a lawyer to help you.
找个律师帮帮你
I understand.
我知道了
Alright then.
行啦
Just take good care
你还是先照顾好
of yourself first.
你自己吧
Chen Wanzhen.
陈婉真
Haven't you finished these yet?
你这些是不是没弄完啊
I'll do it.
我来 我来
You haven't transferred to sales yet.
还没转销售部呢
Shouldn't you at least finish
是不是应该把活
your work first?
都干完了呀
Ms.,should this water
姐
be placed in this room?
这水是放这个屋吗
I'll do it.
我 我来
It'll be done soon.
一会儿就好了
I'll take you there.
我带你去
Okay.
好
She really thinks she's special.
还真把自己当盘菜了
Mom.
妈
I finished my homework.
我作业都写完了
But you haven't finished yours.
你还没写完呢
Try doing homework
让你一个人写仨人作业
for three people.
你试试
Why should I do homework for three?
我为啥要写仨人作业呀
And our teacher
而且我们老师
wouldn't agree that.
肯定不会同意的
That's the difference
所以啊
between a boss and a teacher.
就是老板和老师的差别
So cherish it.
珍惜吧
Study hard,
好好学习
or one day
要不然有一天
you'll work for a boss.
老师变老板
Then you'll have something to cry about.
就有你哭的了
I knew it.
我就知道
You always end up saying
你什么事情都能绕到
"study hard."
好好学习这四个字上
All moms are like this.
妈都这样
Dad, sign this for me.
爸 你给我签
Is my handwriting that bad?
是我字写得不好吗
Ask your mom.
你让你妈签
Her signature looks great.
你妈字签得多好看哪
Don't you feel guilty?
你良心不痛吗
What are you saying?
你这孩子 你说什么呢
So rude.
没大没小的
Fine, I'll sign it myself.
得了 我自己签
What are you doing?
你要干吗
What's wrong?
怎么了
She wants to sign it herself.
她要自己签
I'll sign it.
我签
I have good handwriting.
我字写得好
At least for my name.
名字还是可以的
Tomorrow, take Yunjie
明天你带云阶
to visit my parents.
回趟我爸妈那儿
My Dad called.
我爸来电话了
He said he wants to cook something nice.
说要做好吃的
What about you?
那你呢
I'm not going.
我不去了
I'll come pick you up later.
我回头去接你们
We need to keep the pregnancy a secret.
怀孕这个事一定要保密
I should also avoid
我也得少在
hanging around them.
他们跟前晃悠
I'm showing signs now.
我现在有反应
They're experienced.
他们都是过来人
They can tell right away.
一看就能看出来
I was just thinking,
我刚才还在想
if there's surgery,
要是手术的话
what about Yunjie?
云阶怎么办
Maybe
要不然
we could send her to my parents' place.
也让她去我爸妈那儿住
Then we can tell them
然后咱们就跟他们说
we're going back to our hometown
要回老家
to visit my sister and brother-in-law.
看大姐大姐夫
It's sister.
大姐
Not answering.
不接
That's not good.
不好吧
It's bedtime.
睡觉了嘛
It's so late.
这么晚
What if something happens?
万一有啥事呢
What could happen?
能有什么事
Sister.
大姐
Are you asleep?
睡了吗
Not yet.
没呢
Li Lin is here too. Look.
李临也在呢 你看
Sis,
姐
you're still awake.
没睡呢
I thought
我一想
you won't go to bed so early.
你们就不能睡那么早
Take a look
看一下
at what I make for you.
大姐 给你们做什么了
Black sesame balls.
黑芝麻丸
Lin and Xu.
临临 小许
Strictly speaking,
严格地说
this isn't really medicine.
这啊 不算药
But it doesn't taste bad.
倒是也不难吃
It's actually very tasty.
特别好吃啊
Black sesame, walnuts, dates,
黑芝麻 核桃 红枣
and donkey-hide gelatin.
还有这个阿胶
They all help nourish and boost blood.
都是补气养血的
Sis.
姐
Well,
这样
if we want something,
我们想吃什么
we'll just buy it ourselves.
我们就自己买
You don't need to worry.
你不用操心
It's not necessary.
没必要
Sis.
大姐
How did you know
你怎么知道
I need to boost my energy and blood?
我要补气血呀
Homemade is
自己家做的
always the best.
肯定特别好
Thank you.
谢谢啊
Please send it to me later.
回头你给我寄过来呗
Meng'an is really understanding.
还是梦安懂事
Meng'an, I heard
梦安 听说
your menopause started early.
你更年期提前了
It's depleting your energy and blood.
就是亏了气血
Just eating these isn't enough.
光吃这些不行的
You need to get a pulse diagnosis.
得号号脉
I'll come over to your place
等我去你们那边坐诊
and give you a proper check-up.
给你好好看看
I'll send it to you later.
回头姐给你寄过去啊
Okay.
好嘞
Alright.
好
Rest well, bye.
休息吧 拜拜
This
这
is unnecessary worry.
瞎操心
What did you say to your sister?
你跟你姐说什么了
I went home last week.
上周回家嘛
Your mom heard about your early menopause
你妈妈听说你更年期了
and insisted I ask brother-in-law
就非得让我去问大姐夫
for a prescription
要个方子
to help you with it.
让你调理调理
Mom told me to call.
妈让我打电话
I couldn't just ignore it.
我不能不打吧
Right?
对吧
I didn't say anything else.
其他的我什么都没有说
Li Lin, I warn you,
李临 我警告你啊
if you dare privately...
你要敢在私底下
It's impossible.
不可能
You know what kind of person I am.
我是什么人 你很清楚
I will never let my sister
我是绝不会让大姐
get involved in our family matters.
掺和到我们家里的事
You know that.
你知道的
That's just how my sister is.
我姐就是这样
Always meddling.
多管闲事
She drives me crazy.
烦死她了
I've been annoyed since I was a kid.
我打小就烦她
She's the one who raised you.
你是姐姐带大的好吧
So heartless.
没心没肺的
We can't be like him.
我们可不能学他啊
This bow
这个蝴蝶结
looks nice, doesn't it?
好看吧
Lin, did you take Meng'an
临临
to see a traditional Chinese doctor
安安那个病
for her illness?
你带她去看中医了吗
My sister
我姐啊
sent some tonics
给梦安寄了一些
for her.
补气血的药
She said next time
说 等下一回
when brother-in-law
姐夫到这儿来
comes here,
出诊的时候
he'll check on her.
给她看看
Don't we have a traditional Chinese doctor here?
那咱们这儿没中医啊
Do we really have to wait until then?
非得等到那个时候看
Fine.
行
She's pretty busy this week.
这周她比较忙
She'll be on vacation next week.
下周她休假了
I'll take her to see a doctor then.
我带她去看看大夫
We're supposed to visit Auntie back home.
不是说回老家看大姑吗
Yeah.
对啊
That's what I said.
我说的就是
Next week
下一周
we'll go back and visit them.
回老家看看他们
By the way,
顺便
we'll ask your uncle
就让你姑父
to check on your mom.
给你妈妈看看病
You have to know that traditional Chinese medicine
你要知道这中医
isn't something that works
不是一次两次
in just one or two sessions.
就能看好的
How long is
那我姐她请了
her annual leave?
多长时间年假呀
Two weeks.
两个星期吧
Two weeks?
两个星期
Why don't you ask her to stay here?
那你让她回来住呗
No need.
不 不用
Staying here would just trouble you all.
在这儿住给你们添麻烦
At home,
在家
I can take good care of her.
我还能好好照顾她
What trouble?
添什么麻烦
Just go back and have a look.
回去看看吧
How long has it been since last visit?
多长时间没回去了
Stay a few more days.
多住两天
See how capable my dad is?
你看我爸厉害吧
He just got a new job,
刚换了新工作
and already he can take a vacation.
就能请假了
There's another one over there.
那儿还有一条
So beautiful, I can't even choose.
真好看 都选不过来了
Are there more of these fish?
还有吗 这鱼
Yes.
有
Mu.
阿木
Come over here.
你来一下
There's some work
有些工作
I need to hand over to you.
我跟你交接一下
Have you submitted promotion application?
升职申请交了吗
Yes, I have.
交了
Thank you, Ms. Xu,
谢谢许总监
for giving me this opportunity.
给我这个机会
It's not me giving you the opportunity.
不是我给你机会
It's the result
这是你自己努力
of your own hard work.
来的结果
This USB drive contains
这个优盘里边呢
several projects
是我们最近
we've been working on recently.
在做的几个项目
I'm taking two weeks off.
我 要休两周假
You'll be in charge of these projects.
这些项目由你来负责
Can I handle it?
我行吗
You won't be around.
您也不在
What if I'm unsure about something?
我要有什么拿不准的
Can I call you?
我能给你打电话吗
Can you call me
你能一辈子
for the rest of your life?
给我打电话吗
Mu,
阿木啊
I have no doubt about your abilities.
你的能力是没问题的
I trust my judgment.
我相信自己的眼光
You must trust yourself even more.
你更要相信你自己
As a department head,
作为一个部门的负责人
besides having strong
除了要有过硬的
professional skills,
业务能力
you also need decisiveness and judgment.
还要有决策力和判断力
More importantly, you need
更重要的
the ability to take responsibility.
是要有承担责任的能力
Understand?
知道吗
Got it.
知道了
If there's something you can't handle,
有搞不定的
you can call me.
可以给我打电话
I will help you.
我会帮你的
Okay.
好
Go ahead.
去吧
Does it look good?
好看吗
Let me see.
我看
It looks great.
真好看
You're wearing too much
你这脖子上还戴着
around your neck.
有点多
We're leaving now.
我们走啦
Come back early, okay?
早点回来啊
Sure.
好
Xin,
心心
we're going for a walk.
我们出去遛弯
Do you want to come with us?
你跟不跟我们
Wanna join us?
一块儿去啊
No, you go ahead.
我不去了 你们去吧
Alright.
行
Take care.
那你好好待着啊
Be safe.
注意安全啊
Don't worry.
放心吧
Why are you here instead
你这不在爸妈家待着
of staying at mom and dad's?
又跑我这儿来干吗呀
Did you get into a fight again?
是又跟谁吵起来了
I came to check on you.
我来看看你呀
Check on me?
看我干吗
What's so interesting about me?
我有什么好看的
You're reacting.
有反应啊
Reacting? What do you mean?
有 什么反应啊
Why are you staring at me like that?
你老这么盯着我干吗呀
Is there something on my face?
我脸上有东西
It's in your belly.
你肚子里有
Who told you?
谁跟你说的
No one told me.
不用谁说
I guessed it myself.
我自己猜的
You have that kind of ability?
你还有那脑子呢
Of course.
那是
While cleaning the yard, mom said
收拾院子的时候 妈说
you were going through menopause
说你更年期了
and asked traditional Chinese doctor
让姐夫家的老中医
to check you out.
给你看看
But brother-in-law was hesitant,
姐夫支支吾吾的
saying it wasn't necessary.
说不用
Then he said Meng'an
说那个梦安
had taken two weeks of vacation.
请了两周的年假
And back to hometown for a check-up.
我带她回老家去看看
That was too funny.
太逗了
I figured it out immediately.
我一听就听出来了
As a workaholic,
你说你一个工作狂
you would you take a vacation
你能因为这么点事
for this?
就请年假
Could I believe it?
我能信吗
It's ridiculous.
开玩笑嘛
Can't even lie properly,
你姐夫是连个谎
can he?
都说不明白吗
No.
不不不
I'm just too smart.
是我太聪明了
I figured it out in an instant.
我一下就看明白了
Sorting vegetables, brother-in-law?
择菜呢 姐夫
Thanks for your hard work.
辛苦你了
No worries.
不辛苦
It's no big deal.
这点活
Need help?
要不我帮帮你
No need.
不用
You go rest.
你歇你的
My sister is pregnant.
我姐怀孕了
And she doesn't want to keep it.
而且她还不想要
I guess it all right.
怎么都被我说中了
I'm telling you, Li Lin.
我告诉你啊 李临
If my sister doesn't want it,
我姐她不想要
you better not force her.
你不许逼她啊
My sister is different from me.
我姐跟我不一样的
She's a career woman.
她是事业女性
The right to choose motherhood
生育权
must be in the hands of
必须要掌握在
us women ourselves.
我们女性自己手里
Got it?
听清楚了吗
Remember that.
记住了啊
Why hire paparazzi?
那你还请什么狗仔呀
I think you're better than them.
我看你比他们强多了
They just take pictures,
他们也就拍拍照
and you also do the analysis.
你还负责分析
I'll continue analyzing.
我接着分析啊
You don't want it, right?
你不要吧
Why wouldn't I want it?
我为什么不要啊
You do want it?
你要啊
You're getting older.
你高龄啊
You're already 40.
你都四十了
So what if I'm 40?
四十怎么了
If I can still get pregnant at 40,
四十我还能怀
it means I'm in good health.
说明我身体好呀
Alright.
行行行
You're amazing.
你厉害
You're healthy.
你身体好
But I'm not discussing
但我现在不跟你讨论
whether you can conceive or not.
怀不怀的问题
I'm discussing
我跟你讨论
whether you should give birth or not.
生不生的问题
You're 40.
你四十了
You give birth,
你生
and after that,
生完之后
can you recover?
缓得过来吗
Will you be able to bounce back?
能恢复得了吗
You can't recover.
你恢复不了
I'm asking you,
我就问你
after giving birth,
你生完孩子之后
will you still work?
你还上班吗
Of course, I'll still work.
我肯定上班啊
I'm not like you.
我又不像你
Fine.
行
You'll work, but you'll need at least
你上班
three to five years to recover, right?
那起码得缓个三五年吧
At least until kid starts school, right?
起码得耗到孩子上学吧
When the child starts school,
等孩子上学了
you won't have to worry business.
你不用管了
By then, you should be retired.
你也该退休了
What job will you still have?
你还上什么班啊
I'm not that old and I won't be retired.
我多大岁数我就退休了
Alright, not that old.
行行 不大不大
Almost 50, maybe.
也就奔五吧
What company
那哪个公司
would hire someone who's nearly 50?
愿意用奔五的员工呀
After all the effort,
好不容易 千辛万苦地
you find a job,
找到了一个工作
and after a few years,
上了没几年
you still retire.
还是退休了
Then why can you have a second child?
那你为什么能生二胎呀
Right now,
我现在
I'm only 34 with my second child.
我现在二胎了才三十四
How old are you?
你多大呀
Can 30 and 40 be the same?
那三十和四十能一样吗
That's a big difference.
那差老鼻子去了
Think about it yourself.
你自己想想
After you gave birth to Yunjie,
你生完云阶之后
was your body the same as before?
你身体跟以前一样吗
Definitely not the same.
那肯定不一样
Exactly.
还是的
And you were only in your 20 back then.
那你那会儿才二十几
Now you're already 40.
你现在都四十了
I now
我现在
can already foresee your future.
都能预想到你的未来
Mr. Zhang.
张总
Sorry to keep you waiting.
久等了
Never mind.
没有 没有 没有
Hello.
你好 你好
I just finished a meeting.
开个会
Take a seat.
快 快坐 快坐 快坐
No worries, just waited a bit.
没有 就等了一会儿
Please have a seat.
您坐坐坐 坐下
Take your time.
慢慢说
Here.
来
Have some tea.
喝口茶
Mr. Zhang.
张总
I'm on the way.
路上了 路上了
Ten minutes.
十分钟
At most ten minutes.
最多十分钟
What are you doing?
你干吗呀
Even the administrator
这周末行政
has to work overtime this weekend?
都要加班了吗
I was just working out there.
我正在那儿健身呢
Mr. Zhang suddenly asked me to come over.
张总突然叫我过来一趟
Do you know who I saw him with
你知道我在咖啡厅
at the café?
见着他跟谁在一块儿吗
Huang Sisi.
黄思思
You knew?
你知道了
Mr. Zhang asked me about her.
张总向我打听过她
There's no news from the headhunter yet.
猎头那边还没有消息呢
But Huang Sisi's resume
不过黄思思这简历啊
is indeed impressive.
做得确实是漂亮
Not just well-crafted...
也不是做得漂亮
She's handled so many projects.
毕竟干过那么多项目
She must have some abilities.
能力应该还是有的
But I've heard
我可听说
she's not an easy one to deal with.
这人不是个省油的灯啊
Over at Blue Ocean,
在蓝海那边
her affair with Mr. Yu
跟于总的绯闻
was quite a scandal.
闹得沸沸扬扬的
She couldn't stay there anymore,
在那儿待不下去了
so she's looking for a new place.
正找下家呢
With someone like her
你说就她这样的
coming to our company,
来咱们公司
is it a good thing
对你来讲
or bad thing for you?
是好事还是坏事
Ask for my opinion, huh?
征询我意见
So give me your stance.
那你给个态度嘛
Objectively speaking,
客观上讲啊
the position of content Deputy Director
内容副总监这个职位
really can't stay vacant.
确实不能一直空着
Got it.
懂了
Mu's promotion request
阿木的升职申请
has already come to me.
已经到我这儿了
I'll go talk to him later.
我一会儿就去找他谈
You should bring it up to Mr. Zhang first.
你呀 先找张总提一嘴
If he settles it with Huang Sisi,
否则他跟黄思思谈妥了
I won't be able to do anything about it.
那我下不去手啊
Wait for me.
等我
Mr. Zhang.
张总
Come in.
来
Is this a good time?
方便吗
I want to talk to you about Mu.
想跟你聊一下阿木的事
Hasn't the layoffs ended?
裁员不结束了吗
And Mu's performance
再说这个阿木表现
has been pretty good.
挺好的
You're going to lay him off?
你要裁他啊
No, I'm not laying him off.
不 不裁他
I just want to talk to you
我是想跟你聊一下
about promoting Mu.
给阿木升职的事
Then let's sit and talk.
那坐着聊
Where do you want to promote him to?
你想把他往哪升啊
Since the Content Department was merged,
这内容部不是合并了吗
we've been missing a Deputy Director.
一直差个副总监
I was thinking
我是想着
that Mu is quite
阿木这孩子吧
steady
挺踏实的
and loyal.
也很忠心
He has a vibrant mindset.
思路很活跃
His approach is different from
跟我们做传统媒体
traditional media.
出来的不太一样
He's been with the company for three years
来公司也三年了
and has always been a good team player.
一直跟我打配合
We've had a good understanding.
也都很默契
So I was thinking
我就想着
maybe we could
是不是能
promote him
提拔他一下啊
to Deputy Director.
当个 副总监
That's quite a leap.
你这提得也太狠了
You just said he's a kid and has only been
你都说他是个孩子了
with the company for three years.
才来公司三年
You want to promote him
你说给他提到
to that position?
这个位置上
His experience is a bit shallow.
这个资历浅了点吧
His experience
资历
is indeed a bit shallow.
是浅了一点
But this is a special time, right?
但是这不是特殊时期吗
The company just finished the layoffs.
公司刚裁员结束
Everyone who needed to go has left.
该走的也都走了
So shouldn't we
那咱是不是
reward someone?
也得奖励一下
Right?
是吧
This could also
这样也能
boost everyone's morale.
给大家伙鼓鼓劲嘛
if you encourage him.
你鼓劲
why not just pay him?
你给钱不就完了吗
Why did you want
你干吗给他
to give him a promotion?
提那么高的位上
Money
那要是能给钱
would be nice.
也挺好
But, you see,
但是我这不是
I need to take a vacation.
要休假了吗
So if I'm
那你
not around,
我要不在的话
someone has to manage the company.
公司得有人管
Wait
不不不
a minute.
你等会儿
When did I
我什么时候
approve your vacation?
批准你休假了
Last time when I asked for leave,
上次我跟您请假的时候
you said,
你可说
after completing that bid,
做完那个投标就
I could take a break.
让我休息的
Did I?
有吗
Mr. Zhang,
老张
that's not quite fair.
那你这样不合适了啊
You're just tired and looking
你就是怕累
for someone to share workload.
找人给你分担
Alright.
行行行
Go on your vacation then.
休假去 休假去啊
The company cover your travel expenses.
那差旅费公司给你报了
All of them?
全额吗
Meals won't be covered.
吃饭就别报了
Who knows what you'll eat?
谁知道你吃什么呀
We'll cover domestic travel expenses,
你这个国内游给你报销
but if you're going abroad, that's on you.
你要出国就算了
Alright, what about Mu?
那 阿木这事
Take a proper vacation,
踏踏实实地休假
and we'll talk when you get back.
回来再说
Anything else?
还有事吗
No, that's it.
没有了
Alright, I'm leaving.
那我走了
Go ahead.
走吧
Don't tell anyone else.
你别跟别人说啊
This is a special perk
这是公司
just for you from the company.
单独给你的福利
Thank you, Mr. Zhang.
谢谢张总
Sighing like that...
唉声叹气的
She seems unhappy with me, huh?
这对我不满啊 这是
Everyone, please stop what you're doing.
大家把手里活先停一下
I have an announcement.
我宣布
Chen Wanzhen is officially
陈婉真从今天开始
joining us starting today.
正式加入我们销售部
Let's give her a warm welcome.
大家欢迎
Hello, everyone.
大家好
Wanzhen,
婉真
this will be your desk from now on.
以后这就是你的工位
And here's your work card.
这个是你的工牌
Thank you, Mr. Qian.
谢谢啊 钱总
After your probation period,
等试用期过了
we'll sign a formal contract.
我们正式签合同
Okay.
好的
Everyone, get back to work.
大家先忙吧
Please take care of me, everyone.
各位多多关照啊
Chen Wanzhen,
陈婉真
make 15 copies
复印十五份
and put them in the meeting room.
放到会议室
Sales department needs them.
我们销售部等着用呢
Okay.
好的
Hello, Mrs. Mo.
喂 莫太太 你好
You've arrived?
您到了
I'll come out right away.
我这就出来了
Mrs. Yu,
于太太
long time no see.
有日子没见了啊
Yeah, it has been a while.
就是啊
Are you
你们家现在
in the real estate business now?
开发房地产了
No.
不是
I'm just working here.
我在这儿打工
I'm doing sales now.
我现在啊 是做销售的
I see.
我知道了
You must have been
你一定在家
resting at home for a long time,
休息了时间长了
and now
然后现在
you're out to experience life.
出来体验生活了
The kids are grown up now,
这孩子大了
so I decided to come out and work.
我呢 想出来工作了
And how's
那你家
Mr. Yu's business going?
于先生的生意怎么样了
It seems like you
好像你们现在
aren't living in the villa area anymore.
不住别墅区了吧
I'm living in the downtown now.
我现在啊 住市区呢
You know,
您不知道
high-rise apartments in the downtown
现在这市区的高层
have very high living standards.
这个公寓啊
Let me tell you,
这个居住的标准特别高
my husband and I
我跟你说啊
are just thinking of buying
我跟我老公两个人啊
an apartment in the downtown for our son.
刚好想给我们儿子
That's great!
买一套市区的房子
Let me take you
那太好了
to see the model unit.
我带你们
Come on.
去看一下样板间啊
Let's go.
走
Mo, come along and have a look.
老莫 走 一起过去看看
You go ahead.
你们先去看吧
I'm waiting for a call.
我等个电话
Okay.
好的
Men are all about work.
男人就是工作
Mrs. Mo, I'll take you there.
莫太 我带你去
Let's go.
走
Sure.
好
Mrs. Mo,
莫太
What type
你看
of layout do you want?
你想要什么样户型
And how big an area?
然后多大面积的
I'll explain everything to you.
我给你好好介绍一下
Sounds good.
好嘞
Mr. Yu,
于总啊
what's going on with your family?
你们家出什么事了
Covering vacation expenses?
报销年假旅游费
Even the stingiest man is spending money.
能让铁公鸡拔毛
Only you could pull this off.
不愧是许总监呀
You've got some skills.
你有本事啊
I think he's feeling guilty.
我觉着他就是心虚
Making up for whole thing of Huang Sisi.
想补偿我黄思思这事
Huang Sisi?
黄思思那事
No chance.
没戏
Any news?
有消息了
Mr. Zhang couldn't win her over.
张总没搞定她
First, she's still
第一
at Blue Ocean and hasn't resigned.
人家在蓝海还没离职呢
Second,
第二
she's already a director there.
人家已经是总监了
In terms of position and salary she wants,
她要的职位和年薪
Mr. Zhang can't meet that.
张总满足不了她
I mentioned the matter with Mu.
我跟他提阿木的事
He did say
他倒是说
he'd make proper arrangements.
会好好安排
So there's still hope!
那就是还有戏呀
You should've done this a long time ago.
你早就应该这样了
Develop your own people.
培养自己的人
Build your own team.
搭建自己的团队
More efficient work.
工作效率高
Isn't that great?
多好呀
And it prevents outsiders
还能避免空降的人
from taking your credit
来摘你桃子
and your share.
分你蛋糕
Does this sound like
这像是一个
something an HR director
人力资源总监
should say?
该说的话吗
In this field,
这个领域
you're not as good as me.
你肯定不如我
I'm just doing it for the company
我这也是为了公司
to build a stable
能够搭建稳定的
and strong talent pipeline, alright?
良好的人才梯队 好吗
As for Huang Sisi,
这黄思思呢
she's competent.
能力行
But she's a bit of a wild card.
但是个不稳定因素
In my opinion,
我的判断啊
even if we hire her,
就算是用
we need to be cautious.
也得慎用
When are you having the surgery?
你什么时候手术啊
I haven't decided yet.
我还没定呢
Still haven't decided.
还没定呢
You're being so indecisive.
你这太磨叽了
That's not like you.
不像你啊
I think you should have the baby.
要我说你赶紧生了得了
If I were you, I'd go for it.
要我是你 我就生
You want a baby?
想要孩子
Just find a man and have one.
自个找男人生去啊
But I need to find one first.
那我也得找得着呀
Aren't men easy to find?
男人还不好找吗
It's actually quite hard.
很难的
I'm doing fine on my own right now.
我现在一个人
I'm quite happy living alone.
过得挺好的
Finding someone
找一个人
might not make my life better.
能比现在过得好吗
If it's going to be worse,
要过得不好
why would I look for someone?
我找他干吗呀
Not necessarily.
也不一定的
Look at me and Li Lin.
你看我跟李临
Aren't we doing just fine?
不就挺好的吗
If all men were like Li Lin,
要都像你们家李临那样
the whole world would be celebrating.
全世界女人都烧高香了
Otherwise, just give Li Lin
要不然你把你们家李临
to me.
让给我
I don't mind that he's a second marriage.
我肯定不嫌弃他是二婚
Get lost.
滚
I'm not done talking.
我还没说完呢
I've decided.
我决定了
When I turn 40,
等我到四十岁的时候
I'll find a man
我找个男人
and have a child.
生个孩子
The thing is
关键
it'll help delay menopause.
还能延缓更年期
But you also need
那你也得
to have a good body like mine.
有我这样的好身体
In this aspect, you're not as good as me.
这方面你就不如我了
Look at me now.
看我现在
Working out
锻炼身体
and delaying aging.
延缓衰老
Mrs. Mo,
莫太
buying a house is a big deal.
这买房是大事
You should think it over.
你们再考虑考虑
It's okay.
没关系的
Here are
这呢
some materials about the property.
是楼盘的一些资料
Take them home and take a look.
你们拿回去看一看
Give it to me.
给我吧
What kind of floor and orientation
你们喜欢什么样的楼层
do you prefer?
什么样朝向
I'll try
我争取啊
to reserve it for you.
帮你们预留出来
Let me know
决定以后
when you decide.
告诉我
You can talk a bit more.
你们再聊一会儿
I'll check if the car has arrived.
我看看车来没来
Goodbye, Mr. Mo.
再见 莫先生
Wanzhen,
婉真啊
your child is still so young,
你说你孩子才多大呀
and you're already working.
你就出来干活
And you're working in sales.
而且干的还是销售
What about
你让你老公的面子
your husband's dignity?
往哪搁呀
I understand how you feel,
你的心情我理解
but our husbands
但是我们的老公
are all in business.
都是做生意的
At least give him some respect.
好歹得给他一点面子吧
It saves you
省得在外面
from being talked about outside.
引起别人说闲话
Mrs. Mo,
莫太
not everyone
不是每个人
is as fortunate as you.
都像你一样好命
Every family has its troubles.
家家有本难念的经
Yes.
也是 也是
I'll leave now.
那我先走了
I'll see you out.
我送送你
Let's go.
走
Chen Wanzhen,
陈婉真
get in the car.
你给我上车
Go home.
回家
What are you doing?
你干吗
Get in the car.
什么干吗 上车
Stop right there.
你给我站住
What are you doing?
你 你干什么
You're really something.
你行啊你
Selling a house
卖房现在卖到
to my friend.
我朋友头上去了
Mrs. Mo is also my friend.
那莫太太也是我的朋友
Do you know?
你知道吗
You're not just
你现在不光是丢了
disrespect yourself.
你自己的脸
You're also disrespecting me.
你还丢了我的脸
Do you know that?
你知道吗
How did I disrespect?
我怎么就丢脸了
Mr. Mo.
莫总
He just called me.
刚才给我打电话了
He asked if
问我是不是
there was a problem with the financing.
融资出了问题
Why is my wife
为什么自己老婆
selling houses here?
跑这儿卖房子来
Mr. Mo is a veteran
人家老莫可是
in the investment field.
这投资界的老人
What he says carries weight.
人家说话很有分量的
Do you know?
你知道吗
How do you expect people to think of me?
你让人家怎么想我
I'm in the middle of financing.
我正融资呢
Yu Hai, I'll say it again.
于海 我再跟你说一遍
I want a divorce.
我要跟你离婚
If you think it's embarrassing
你要是觉得我出来卖房
that I'm selling houses,
给你丢脸了
or if it makes people doubt
或者让人怀疑
your abilities,
你的实力了
I'll find a way to clear things up.
我会找机会给你澄清
I'll say that you are
说你于海现在是
a bachelor
单身王老五
and that your ex-wife didn't take
你前妻没有
a single share in your company.
拿你公司半毛钱股份
It won't
对你事业不会
affect your career.
造成任何影响
Is that good enough?
总可以了吧
Enough talk.
别废话啊
Quit your job now.
现在你给我辞职去
Let go of me.
你放开我 你
Are you out of your mind?
脑子有病吧
Mr. Zhang,
张总
I'm fine.
我没事啊
Zhenghao Teahouse, right?
正好茶楼是吧
Okay.
行行行
I'll be right over.
我这就过来
Yes.
是
Thank you for introducing
谢谢您上次给我介绍
so many good friends last time.
那么多好朋友啊
Got it.
好嘞
I'll have the driver come downstairs.
我这就让司机下楼
I'll be right there.
我这就过去啊
What's wrong with you?
你怎么回事啊
Shopping should be fun.
购物多快乐呀
Why do you always look so gloomy?
你怎么一直垮着个脸
You're right.
你说对了
I'm not happy at all
我现在啊
right now.
一点都不快乐
Why?
为什么
I'll let you in on a secret.
我告诉你个秘密
But don't tell anyone.
你可别告诉别人啊
Yunjie.
云阶
He Lu.
何璐
I'm here.
我来了
I came at the right time, didn't I?
我来得及时吧
I know you guys are tired from shopping.
知道你们逛街累了
I brought you milk tea.
特意给你买的奶茶
Yunjie.
云阶
You like this one.
你喜欢这个
He Lu, you're this one.
何璐 你是这个
Is that right?
对吧
Why does it always
怎么每次出现
seem so surprising
这个时间点
when you show up?
都这么让人诧异呢
Let's go.
走
What's so surprising?
我怎么诧异了
I showed up just in time.
我出现多好啊
I brought you milk tea when you're tired.
你们累了给你们买奶茶
Wait a moment.
等我一下
Here you go.
给你
Thanks, Wu.
谢谢老吴啊
Clock out when it's time.
到点就下班
We're not a state-owned enterprise.
当我们国营单位呢
Isn't it off-duty time now?
现在不是下班时间吗
Besides, my work
再说我的工作
is already done.
已经完成了
There's no need to work overtime.
没什么需要加班的
I have a viewing group later.
我待会儿还有看房团呢
You need to handle the reception.
你不得负责接待啊
Fei.
菲菲
Mr. Sun.
孙主任
It'll be fine when I'm here.
我在这儿就行
Aren't you picking up the kids?
你不要接孩子吗
Hurry up.
赶紧的
That's not possible.
那可不行
Mr. Qian just said
刚才钱副总说了
that
指定
Wanzhen needs to stay for learning.
让婉真姐留下来学习
You can't just work
销售
nine to five in sales.
哪有朝九晚五下班的呀
Look here.
您看看
In our sales department,
我们这销售岗位
no one leaves on time.
一个都没走吧
Do you really want to switch roles?
你到底要不要转岗啊
How about this?
要不这样
Wanzhen, after picking up the kids,
婉真
come back right away.
接完孩子以后马上回来
I'll keep an eye on things here for you.
我在这儿替你盯会儿
Is that okay?
行吗
Never mind, Mr. Sun.
不了 孙主任
I'll handle it myself.
还是我自己想办法吧
Thank you.
谢谢您啊
And she still wants to switch to sales.
就这还要转销售呢
Hello, Wanzhen.
喂 婉真姐
Mengxin.
梦心
Sorry.
不好意思
I'm asking another favor.
又得麻烦你了
I have to work overtime today.
我今天要加班
Could you pick up Wan and Zhen
一会儿你能顺便去
on your way?
接一下婉婉 真真吗
No problem.
没问题啊
I'm already at the school,
我现在已经在学校
waiting for them.
等着他们放学呢
That's great.
太好了
Let them play
那让她俩
at your place for a while.
在你家玩一会儿
I'll pick them up
我下班以后
after work.
马上去接她们
It's fine, don't worry.
没事 你放心
You focus on your work.
你踏踏实实地上班
Xiong wants to play
熊熊还想多跟
with the older kids a bit longer.
小姐姐们玩一会儿呢
Thank you, Mengxin.
谢谢啊 梦心
No need to be polite.
客气什么
If anything like this happens again,
以后有这种事
just call me anytime.
随时给我打电话啊
I'll let you know
那我接上了
once I've picked them up.
给你发信息啊
Okay.
好嘞
Bye.
挂了
Bought the favorite toy car.
喜欢的小车买回来
Come on, Yunjie.
来 云阶
Come in quickly.
快进来
Grandson.
大孙子
In a moment...
待会儿
Hello, Grandma.
奶奶好
Hello.
你好 你好
Let's go.
走吧 走吧
Hurry up.
快走
This is the secret you told me
这就是你跟我说
about your family?
你家的秘密啊
You're my best friend.
你是我闺蜜
That's why I told you.
我才告诉你的
You have to keep it a secret.
你可得帮我保守秘密啊
Don't worry.
放心吧
As your best friend,
你把我当闺蜜
I'll definitely keep it confidential.
我肯定给你保密
Good.
好
You sit over there for now.
你先去那儿坐着
I'll get you some snacks.
我去给你拿零食
Alright.
好嘞
Here.
来
You have so many snacks at home.
你家这么多零食呀
These aren't mine.
这都不是我的
They're the little prince's.
这都是皇太子的
Why do you always call your brother
你怎么老叫你弟
the little prince?
皇太子呀
Before he was born,
在他出生之前
I didn't even know
我也不知道家里
we had a throne to inherit.
有皇位要继承啊
Once he was born,
这他一出生呀
I was completely sidelined.
我就彻底失宠了
When I visited your house before,
我之前来你家
I hadn't heard
也没听说过
that you had a younger brother.
你有个弟弟呀
Not just you,
别说是你了
even I only
我也是我弟
met my brother
长到一岁的时候
when he was one year old.
才见到他
Seriously?
真假的
My parents had the second child
我爸妈生二胎
without telling me.
是瞒着我生的
At that time, my parents tricked me,
当时我爸妈都骗我说是
saying that my mom had just gained weight.
我妈发胖了
Her belly was so big.
这肚子都这么大了
I actually believed it.
我当时还信了
Later on,
后来
when my mom went back to her hometown,
我妈一回老家
she stayed for several months.
就是好几个月
When she came back,
等到她再回来的时候
my brother
我弟
appeared out of nowhere.
从天而降
No wonder.
怪不得呢
I never
我说之前来你家
saw your brother before.
怎么没见过你弟呢
He was staying in the hometown before
我弟之前一直是在老家
with my grandmother.
跟着我奶奶
Now,
这现在呀
since he's starting kindergarten,
要上幼儿园了
we brought him back.
才要把他带回来
Your brother seems pretty well-behaved.
我看你弟挺乖的呀
He even brought
还给你进贡了
you snacks.
这么多好吃的呢
Be grateful.
知足吧
What's so great about it?
乖什么呀
All these snacks
这一桌好吃的
are all bought by my grandma
全都是我奶奶
for my brother.
给我弟买的
But when I wanted a five-yuan hairpin,
结果我要五块钱的发卡
my grandma wouldn't buy it for me.
我奶都不给我买
Anyway,
反正
if my grandma won't give me money,
我奶奶不给我钱
I just ask her son for it.
我就找她儿子要
Eat more.
多吃点
I really didn't notice
真没看出来
that your grandma is so biased.
你奶奶这么偏心呀
Of course.
可不嘛
It's all about carrying on family line.
我奶奶说是要传宗接代
But that's not right.
不对啊
Isn't it the woman who has the baby?
不是女的生孩子吗
You're right. But you can't
是女的生孩子
have your mother's last name.
但你不可能跟你妈姓吧
So my grandma says
所以我奶奶说呀
only boys can carry on the family line.
这男孩才能传宗接代
Girls,
这女孩呢
are someone else's.
都是别人家的
What century is this?
这都什么年代啦
Such feudal thinking!
什么封建思想呀
Anyway, my grandma says
反正我奶奶说呀
that money
这钱嘛
is reserved for Lulu
是要给璐璐留一点的
as a dowry in the future.
以后当嫁妆用
But the car and the house
但是这车子 房子
are all for my eldest grandson.
可都是留给我大孙子的
Your grandma looks quite kind.
你奶奶看着挺慈祥的呀
But the things she says
那说那话都
are really hard to explain.
真是一言难尽
If you're the only child in your family,
你们家就你一个孩子
you won't have a sense of crisis.
你当然没有危机意识了
No one's competing with you,
也没人跟你争
or trying to take anything from you.
没人跟你抢的
But that's not the case for me.
我就不行了
Have your parents talked to you
你爸妈跟你聊过
about having a second child?
生二胎的话题吗
My mom is already in menopause.
我妈都更年期了
What about menopause?
更年期怎么了
I read online that
网上说
women can't have babies after menopause.
女人更年期之后
That's actually a good thing.
不能再生孩子了
What's so good about it?
这不挺好
It's a condition that needs treatment.
好啥呀
It's quite troublesome.
这是病 得治
My mom still has to
可麻烦了
take time off
我妈现在还得
to see a doctor.
请假去看病呢
And they say
而且都说
that women in menopause have bad tempers.
更年期的女人脾气不好
My mom already had a bad temper.
我妈本来脾气就不好了
It's probably going to get worse.
这估计变本加厉
I'll have a hard time in the future.
我以后日子不好过了呀
Why is everything so difficult?
怎么都这么困难呀
Every family has its own troubles.
家家有本难念的经啊
Just forget about it.
撞死得了
Dinner's ready, Yunjie.
吃饭啦 云阶
Today we're having braised ribbon fish.
今天烧了红烧带鱼
Isn't your mom working overtime?
你妈不是加班吗
You can eat at here.
在阿姨家吃吧
Stay and have dinner.
今天留我家吃饭吧
Spend a bit more time with me.
再多陪陪我
Alright.
好吧
They're not coming back to eat.
都不回来吃
Should I still cook?
那我还做吗
Go ahead and cook.
做吧
Who is it?
谁啊
It's me, your brother-in-law.
姐夫 我啊
Haowen.
浩文
Great.
太好啦
You've brought something again.
又带东西来
Of course.
应该的 应该的
Come on in!
快点来
Okay.
好好好
I was just about to cook.
我正好要做饭
Where's my sister?
姐呢
She's
她
working overtime.
加班
And...
然后
What about Yunjie?
云阶呢
She went to He Lu's house.
去同学何璐家了
Look,
你看
so many dishes.
这么多菜
Isn't it a coincidence?
是不是很巧
Don't cook.
别做啦
I'll take you out to eat.
我请你出去吃吧
I don't want to eat out.
不出去吃
I'll be done here soon.
我这很快就得
Just sit for a while.
你坐一会儿就行了
So troublesome.
麻烦死
For what?
俩人做什么做
The smoke from the oil is unbearable.
这油烟熏得跟什么似的
Cooking is not a hassle for me.
我做饭 我不麻烦
I'll treat you to a big meal.
我请你吃大餐
Is it more barbecue?
又是烤串
You choose.
你挑
Is that true?
真假的
Why would I lie to you?
真的 我骗你干吗
Let's go.
走吧 走吧
Hmm.
这这
I
那我
have to change clothes.
还非得让我换衣服
Change clothes.
换衣服
Alright, hurry up.
行行行 快点吧你
Soup is coming.
汤来喽
Yunjie,
云阶啊
I have already talked
阿姨已经跟你妈妈
to your mom.
说好了
Just enjoy
你就安心
your meal at here.
在阿姨家吃饭啊
Thank you.
谢谢阿姨
You're welcome.
别客气 快吃吧
Eat up.
你妈看上去
Your mom seems
脾气挺好的呀
to have a good temper.
那是你没见过
You haven't seen her
她发火的时候
when she's angry.
最近
she and my grandma...
她和我奶
Mom,
妈
you secretly gave Rui
你又偷偷
bone-strengthening powder again?
给瑞瑞吃壮骨粉了
That's all hormones and it's not good.
这都是激素 不能吃
Our child
咱们家孩子
is shorter than others.
长得比别人家的孩子矮
Eating it might make him a bit stronger.
吃这个能长得壮一点啊
Hormones won't help him
激素吃多了
grow taller.
也长不了个儿
The children of your eldest sister
你大姑姐家的孩子
all took it.
都吃了
Would I harm my
难道我会害我的
precious eldest grandson?
宝贝大孙子
That's all hormones and it's not good.
这都是激素 不能吃
Come on, eat.
来来 吃
They haven't sat down yet.
她们还没坐呢
Don't touch the chopsticks yet.
不许动筷子
It's fine.
没事
Ever since He Rui came back,
我家自从何瑞回来
it's been like this.
都是流水席
My mom and grandma are chasing
我妈和我奶呀
after He Rui every day to feed him.
就每天追着何瑞喂饭
My dad just avoids them if he can.
我爸是能躲就躲
Yunjie's here.
云阶来啦
Hello.
叔叔好
Sit down.
坐 坐
Son.
儿子
You eat first.
你们先吃
come over here.
过来
Stop arguing.
别吵了
You need to help us settle this.
你给我们俩评评理
Help us settle this.
你给我们评评理
Look at mom.
你看看妈
Look at this.
你看看
Can you stop arguing with mom?
你能不能别和妈吵了
I've been busy all day.
我这忙一天
Now I have to mediate your arguments.
回来还得给你们断官司
Two people at home
家里两个人
can't even take care of one child.
连个孩子也看不好
Since He Rui came back,
自从何瑞回来
our home
我们家
has been chaotic every day.
每天都是鸡飞狗跳的
Let's eat first.
咱们先吃
Ignore them for now.
不管他们了
We've got a viewing later.
待会儿接待一个看房团
Is everything ready?
都准备好了吗
It's ready.
准备好了
If I close a deal today,
今天我要是开单
I'll treat everyone to a meal.
请所有人吃饭
Fei is so generous.
菲姐大气
Mr. Qian,
钱总
I'd like to ask for your help.
我想请您帮个忙
Of course.
你说
Let's talk over there.
过去说吧
Mr. Qian,
钱总
could you help me
能请您帮我
get some permissions? I need you
开个权限吗
to reserve a few apartments for me.
帮我预留几套房
Which ones do you need?
你要哪几套
Building 1,
一号楼的
Building 6,
六号楼
Building 7, and Building 3.
七号楼和三号楼
The ones you want are all prime locations.
你要的这些都是好位置
Looks like you're picking up
那看来你做销售
sales quickly.
上手还挺快
But if I reserve these
但是我要把这几套
for you,
都留给你
others might have an issue.
其他销售该有意见了
I've been with the company
我来咱们公司
for some time now.
有段时间了
I think our sales team needs
我觉得咱们销售团队呢
a bit of competition
也需要鲶鱼效应
to motivate everyone.
才能激励
Now that I'm switching roles,
那我现在转岗
I will definitely
肯定会动到
affect the earnings
其他销售的蛋糕
of the other salespeople.
我就是那条鲶鱼
So I hope you can
所以希望你能够
give me the maximum
给我最大的
resource support.
资源支持
This way
这样
my performance will look great,
我的业绩好看
and your profits
那你的利益
will also be maximized.
也能得到最大化
Wanzhen,
婉真
you're good at negotiating.
你这条件谈得不错呀
So, tell me,
那你说说
what's your plan?
你想怎么当这条鲶鱼
I want to hold a viewing event,
我想召开一次看房会
to leverage my resources
把我的资源人脉呢
and turn them into performance.
集中变现
So, I need your full support.
所以需要你的大力支持
Sure.
好啊
Just make sure it's well-organized here.
这边弄好一点啊
Mr. Zhou,
周总
the usual?
还是老样子
Yangchun noodles?
阳春面
Add a marinated egg for me today,
今天给我加个卤蛋
and some luncheon meat.
还有午餐肉
Got it.
我明白
This way, please.
这边请
Thank you.
好 谢谢
Please wait a moment.
您稍等
Your noodles will be ready soon.
您的面马上就好
Okay.
好的
Please give me the noodles
帮我把刚才客人
that the guest just ordered.
那碗面加上来
Mr. Zhou.
周总
What a coincidence.
这么巧
You're here for dinner too?
您也过来吃晚饭
I came for a bowl of noodles.
我来吃碗面
The Yangchun noodles here are delicious.
这儿的阳春面特别好吃
You know it serves great noodles too?
您也知道这儿面好吃啊
Come, have a seat.
来 坐
Sure.
好嘞
That was quick.
这么快就上啦
Sir, your noodles.
先生 您的面
Put it here.
放这儿
It's the noodles I ordered.
我点的面
Alright.
行
The noodles I just ordered
我刚跟您点的
are the same kind.
是一样的面
I ordered Yangchun noodles with extras.
我是加料的阳春面
With a marinated egg and luncheon meat.
加了卤蛋 午餐肉
I also ordered
我也是加的
a marinated egg and luncheon meat.
卤蛋和午餐肉